Ompal Singh (Front-End Developer)

CA-Sector-62 Noida, Uttar Pradesh, PA-Basantpur Danda, Dist.-Sambhal Uttar Pradesh

+91 9627648487 ompalsingh79832@gmail.com ompalsingh79832 linkedin.com/in/omyadav1234/

About Me

Mid-level front-end developer, passionate and focused on responsive web development. Enjoy challenges and love to explore new things. Experience working with both software house and in-house app company. Adapted the agile working culture in the project development flow. Commitment towards what is responsibled for , and willing to do extra.

Experience

Technove Global Software Pvt.Ltd | Front-End Developer

To plan and design the structure and design of responsive web pages.

- Responsible on developing new features, maintaining, and update website.
- To strategize design choice according to user experience.
- Worked closely with back-end developers and UX/UI designers to deliver seamless user experiences.
- Experience in website deployment to server including purchase domain and hosting.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams in an Agile environment to deliver high-quality web applications.

Maya Web Technology | Web Developer

Mav2023-Oct2023

Nov 2023 - Present

- Manage website development projects from initial design through completion, optimising all cross browser and multi-platform compatibility.
- Work closely with programmers and clients to meet project requirement, goals desired functionality.
- Enhanced user experience and accomplish web page objectives by created site structure, navigation, page optimisation and graphics integration.
- Participated in daily stand-ups and sprint planning meetings in an Agile development environment, contributing to project planning and execution.

Internship

RS Technology | Web Developer Intern

Nov2022-Apr2023

- · Utilized HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and frameworks like React and Next.js to develop and maintain web
- Completed internal training on advanced JavaScript concepts and React hooks, enhancing my ability to build dynamic and interactive web applications.
- Proficient in building dynamic web application experience in react component, state management, reactrouter-dom, props and JavaScript fundamentals skilled in debugging and collaborating effectively. Ready for real-world development challenge.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- · Redux Tool kit
- CSS3 • HTML5
- Bootstrap
- MUI
- React.is · Git and Github
- Next.js

Soft Skills

- Team Work
- Problem Solving
- Decision Making
- · Adaptability
- Critical Thinking

Projects

Restaurant Website Fully Responsive and user friendly.

Technology Used - React.js, Bootstrap, CSS3.

IT Company Website Fully Responsive and user friendly.

Technology Used - React.js, Bootstrap, CSS3 and MUI

Loan Bazzar Website

Technology Used - React.js, Bootstrap, CSS and Next.js

Personal IT Website Project

Technology Used - JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap and CSS.

miam.mayawebtech.in

technove.co.in

loanbazar.technove.co.in

omgeniustech.com

Education

Bachelor of Technology (Computer Science & Engineering) ITM College Aligarh (AKTU), UP

2019 - 2023

Senior Secondary School (PCM) BRS Inter College Babrala (UP Board) 2017 - 2019